I'm heading out.
Okay.
Feed Oscar, please.
Have fun while I'm gone.
Why does Oscar look so weak?
Is he hungry?
Why didn't you...
feed Oscar...
I don't like that woman.
Dad, (Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
can't you break up with her?
Then should I...
go back to Mom?
I used to feel tired but proud after work,
but now I'm walking on eggshells
around the director,
and it feels uncomfortable.
Right? We have way fewer expecting mothers.
I like that it's quiet lately.
Hey, being quiet means
they don't need this many staff.
Especially us.
We're feeling down and have energy to spare,
so should we go out for a team dinner?
- Sounds good.
- Let's do it.
I'm in.
- Where to?
- I want tripe.
I want lamb skewers.
- How many rounds?
- Yes, Do Hyun.
- We have to go at least three rounds.
- Of course.
- First round, lamb skewers.
- Tripe, lamb skewers.
Uh, I just finished work...
Do Hyun, are you drunk? At this hour?
We're going to have a blast.
Do Hyun.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to walk a bit?
Daniel kept saying he was okay.
He just kept insisting
he was fine,
so I...
Obviously, there's no way
he could be okay.
But I honestly didn't know.
Of course you didn't know.
No one ever knows.
They hide it desperately
without saying a word.
I...
I want to get along with Daniel.
Why?
Do you think it won't work?
No...
I...
just don't know what to do...
I'll do it.
Daniel has his own way and pace,
so I don't know when or what it'll be,
but I'll keep looking for an opportunity.
Who knows? It might be sooner than we think.
I really...
didn't expect you...
to say that.
Daniel's feelings...
I can't...
do anything about them,
and it'll be hard on you, too.
I keep worrying... what if you leave me?
What if you abandon me?
You really are an artist.
No joke.
[Catholic Church]
Two single adults
spent the night together.
With mutual consent.
What's the problem?
It's not
a problem, strictly speaking...
Was it a one-time fling?
Oh, no!
- It wasn't really a fling...
- Then it must be love.
Well...
it's not exactly love, either...
What is troubling you
the most right now?
We first met in kindergarten.
And?
I mean...
If things go south,
I'm afraid it'll ruin
our 20-year friendship.
So what if it does?
Excuse me?
I asked, so what if a 20-year friendship ends?
Well...
[For the Faithful]
Occupied.
Hey,
get out of here.
Huh?
I said, get out.
Aren't you too old
to be getting beaten up like this?
I didn't get beaten up, Father.
It was an act of punishment and revenge.
Jeez...
Like father, like son. You're just like him.
What?
Just call me Hyung, like the old days.
Okay... Hyung.
So...
It's between love and friendship. Right?
That same old cliche.
You can't really sum us up that simply, but...
You know about Jun Kyung and me
back in our school days, right?
Can you call that a relationship?
If anything,
she wasn't into you.
You chased her around spreading rumors,
then my mom threw water on you.
Back in my prime, full of energy...
why did I give up on Jun Kyung
instead of enduring that humiliation?
What?
I chose friendship back then.
I was torn between love and friendship.
For the sake of some great friendship...
Hey.
- You were never her type.
- Shut up.
Friendship, my foot.
You just lacked the courage and confidence.
It's nothing more than a loser's excuse.
Do you honestly not like her?
Why worry if you don't like her?
He looks perfectly fine.
What a complete moron.
Listen up!
It's sudden, but...
Our marketer, Hwang Beom Jun,
just handed in his resignation.
He feels bad, so he's treating us tonight.
Let's all go out after work.
Let's make him spend big before he goes.
He said he's buying something expensive!
See you later! I'll treat you to a great meal!
That is so cool...
Quitting for love...
and leaving for Europe indefinitely.
I wish I were your age, Beom Jun.
It's not too late
for you yet, Chief.
I don't have the courage. Or the talent.
Talent wouldn't be enough, anyway.
Only people who work for fun can do that.
So, where in Europe are you going?
She said she wants to visit Estonia,
so we'll start with the Baltic states.
The Baltic states...
I've only heard of them in books.
Where are the Baltic states?
- Is she leaving?
- Is she heading out?
I guess so.
I'm telling you, that's not it.
Drop it.
- I'm sick of hearing that.
- Oh, cake!
What?
See? That's the spirit.
It is a farewell party, after all.
- Really?
- Did she slip out to get that cake?
Congratulations.
Have a great trip to Europe
with your girlfriend.
Thank you...
Right...
You're just being true to your feelings.
I'm the idiot.
What the...
- What?
- What was...
- What's going on?
Why did she do that?
So for Ms. Oh Mi Ja's 80th birthday...
Got it.
I'm not that stingy.
If you order over 300 towels,
I'll just throw everything in for you.
Quiet down, I'm on the phone.
No, no! Yes, go ahead.
Right.
We'll do that for you. Okay, thank you.
- Jin Ho.
- What?
What brings you here without calling?
Hey.
Hello.
You got my text, right?
Yes.
100 each of gray, pink, and white...
Yes. Please have them ready by the 15th.
Thank you.
Please understand.
You know how she is.
What's wrong with her?
She's the best.
Did all the nice people die off?
I'm not asking her to be soft like a new towel.
But
she shouldn't be scratchy
like a scrub towel.
What about a scrub towel?
You scared me.
When did you get here?
What about the shop?
It's empty. So you go. Hurry.
What?
Okay...
I'll come visit you soon.
When she first brought you home to get married,
everyone was against it. It was chaos.
- I'm sure they were.
- Right.
I mean, considering your ages back then...
But you know I was the only one
who approved?
Of course. I know.
My sister asked me why I approved.
What do you think I told her?
I said you looked tacky,
so you wouldn't be popular with women.
Meaning
you would never cheat.
I don't know what to say in this situation...
But, really... It's a genuine
- misunderstanding.
- No.
You don't have the guts to cheat
while my sister is still alive.
Why wouldn't I know?
My husband just laughs it off
when people don't pay him.
I've watched that for over 20 years.
Maybe I'm just selfish...
but seeing my husband makes my blood boil.
If
he had an accident and ended up like that...
and I had to change his diapers
for seven years...
and put up with that temper...
there is no way
I could've done that.
But he probably would.
Because he's a fool.
Even if we're family...
I only thought about my poor sister.
I never thought
about how hard it was for you.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
I still can't congratulate you on that woman...
I won't until the day I die...
But thank you
for taking care of my sister.
Thank you so much.
- Get home safe.
- Bye.
Stop mumbling.
- Is this fun?
- Yeah, it's fun!
Let's go for round two!
Why are you always sitting over there?
Is this the only place you have to go?
Do you think my house is a joke?
Why are you
being so prickly?
Why are you here?
What happened to your face?
I asked why you're here.
I thought I should apologize.
Apologize for what?
I just
broke up with Sol recently...
- And...
- Forget it.
My feelings are my own.
I don't expect anything from you.
So you don't need to say more.
Okay...
Actually,
there is one thing.
What is it?
- Anything I can do...
- Tell them
you'll do the internship again.
- What?
- You said you regretted
doing nothing before your mom passed away.
And you know I played a part in that, right?
So get it back
and buy me a proper meal.
And
stop walking on eggshells!
Some people quit their jobs and act so proud.
They break up on a whim
and go to Europe together.
But look at us...
Why are we such idiots?
Ugh!
You have no idea how happy I am.
That you came
to see me like this.
Daniel.
I came because I have something to say.
What?
Hey, kid!
Watch where you're going.
What are you doing? He fell and got hurt.
I didn't hit him.
He fell on his own.
He's just a kid! Like you said.
You should've asked if he was okay first.
Cars drive through here...
He shouldn't be riding that...
Who are you, anyway?
Are you his mom?
Yes.
I am his mom.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
For saying you're my mom earlier?
No.
For not asking if you were okay first,
or if you were hurt.
Even though I had plenty of chances.
I asked Dad
to break up with you.
I...
regretted it.
Why?
I don't like you,
but I don't want Dad to be sad, either.
You don't like me either, right?
Who likes someone who hates them?
Ouch!
Wear protective gear from now on.
But
that doesn't look cool.
I'm hungry.
Do you want to go eat?
Isn't it spicy?
I'm practicing.
If it's spicy, just don't eat it. Why practice?
Because I want to get along...
with people.
Can I ask you something?
Why Oscar?
The fish's name.
Do I...
have to say?
It's the name
of a kid
who bullied me in Germany.
The kid I hated the most.
Ah...
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'll change the name.
No.
I like that name.
Is it better now?
Did the milk help?
It's my first time, but it's pretty good.
First time?
He never bought it for you?
It's good. Eat up.
It's so good.
What is this?
You're only serving the Guide.
That's the tyranny
of the one holding the tongs.
Oh, it's not tyranny...
So don't just give me some.
You should eat, too, Jin Ho.
What?
- Eat up.
- What's going on with you two?
What is it?
The way you look at each other is suspicious.
Wait...
Are you dating the Guide or something?
Excuse me?
He's not denying it.
No way!
What?
For real?
- What?
Yes. We're dating.
Why don't you sing a song?
I'm a terrible singer. You sing another one.
Do you think you're at a concert?
Pay the entrance fee or start singing.
Pick one!
- I'm not good...
- Pick one.
Just sing one song.
I'll do it. I'll sing.
You look really happy today.
Yes. I am.
Right.
We only took that one trip together,
but here we are,
the whole group still meeting up,
laughing, and supporting each other.
The reason I was truly happy today
is that we didn't hide our relationship.
We didn't have to care what others thought.
Me too.
Ja Yeong...
I have a favor to ask.
If you do me a favor first,
I'll listen.
Okay.
Tell me. I'll do it.
Sing a song for me.
What?
No way...
I really can't sing.
Then I can't grant your favor, either.
Come on... That's not fair.
How about I give you a piggyback ride instead?
No.
I'm really bad at it.
Okay then, don't laugh.
Now?
Right here?
Then where and when else should I do it?
Don't laugh.
Promise me.
Promise.
Just stay...
Don't laugh.
♪ Just stay ♪
♪ by my side ♪
♪ You must not ♪
♪ leave ♪
♪ Leaving longing ♪
♪ behind on the long road ♪
♪ You can't return ♪
♪ in search of a rainbow ♪
♪ In the cold wind ♪
♪ that blows ♪
♪ You cry alone ♪
♪ But I'll always stay ♪
♪ by your side ♪
♪ I'll never leave you ♪
I really can't sing, can I?
No.
It was wonderful.
Really?
Now,
tell me your favor. I'll grant it.
Well,
Ja Yeong...
You see...
Dinner with your family?
If it feels like too much, we can wait a while.
Too much? Why would it be too much?
Really?
Then bring Daniel along.
I told Dad and Jun Seo about Daniel.
Ah! If Daniel says he wants to...
let's all meet together.
Thanks for driving me home.
I'm the one who should be thankful today.
You're just saying thanks?
Aren't you forgetting something?
Dad?
Yeah.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Ah, yes.
Dad.
Yeah.
You should have called before coming.
I had a gathering nearby
and just stopped by.
That guy was handsome.
- Ah...
- He made a good impression.
Right.
- Here are some tissues.
- Oh, thanks.
I'll get it.
He really seemed like a nice guy.
Ah, yeah. Right.
- Hey, so...
You go first.
You say it first.
Actually, I'll go first.
Do you want to have dinner
with Ja Yeong sometime?
Is it too sudden?
I don't mean to pressure you. It's just...
I'd love to.
Let's have dinner.
Are you sure?
- Go in.
- Yes.
Hey.
Yeah?
Never mind. Go in.
- Dad...
- Go in.
- Ah, yes... Get home safe.
- Okay.
Here is a story from listener "Midnight."
Back when I worked the dawn shift
at a convenience store,
there was a customer
who always came in at the same time,
wearing the same clothes to buy the same beer.
What?
She never spoke,
and never showed any emotion.
Seeing her
felt like looking at myself.
I think dawn is like that.
A time when you can't hide anything.
During the day, we pretend
to be happy or pretend not to be lonely.
We can hide somewhere in between
whether we are happy or lonely.
But you can't do that at dawn.
It's the time that lets you know for sure
that you aren't in that middle ground.
- She didn't ask anything...
- and didn't say anything.
It was just comforting.
Because she stayed with me...
Because she was like me,
I wanted to say thank you,
but I couldn't.
She didn't come to buy beer
at that time anymore.
I thought it was a relief.
It seemed like she wasn't lonely anymore.
Thank you.
If we happen to meet next time,
I'll buy you a beer.
Didn't you say you didn't need any of it?
Yes.
I did say that.
That was barely a week ago. Just a week.
Did you suddenly need it all again?
I thought I didn't need any of it,
but I realized something important remained.
Somehow, I thought you were too sentimental
for a STEM major.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it embarrassing to go back on your word
like this?
It is embarrassing.
Gosh.
Should I consider this effort?
It's so hard to be fair.
Hey.
Did Professor Park's blurb come in?
- Yes. I sent it to the printers a moment ago.
- Okay.
- Marketing.
- Yes.
Have you checked the interview schedule?
Yes. Checking it right now.
Let's speed things up.
Sure.
I decided to be an intern again.
Thanks to you then, and thanks to you now.
Where's the Ssamjang?
Oh, here it is.
Oh my, Raphael.
Hello.
Father.
Fancy meeting you here.
Right.
We're taking Father to visit a new believer.
Yes.
How have you been doing lately?
Thanks to your prayers, I'm doing well.
You look so much better.
You must be much more at peace now.
Yes, thanks to you all.
But they say that's not always the case.
They say the first year after bereavement
is the most dangerous time.
Let's finish shopping.
I'm just so worried.
Father.
- We should visit Raphael's house too...
- Jin Ho.
Is this enough?
Who is she?
Well...
This is my girlfriend.
Ja Yeong, please say hello.
This is the Father from my church,
the lady I mentioned,
and other fellow members.
Please say hello.
Hello.
Well, we need to finish shopping.
Yes, go ahead.
Honey, shall we go over there?
Oh! Sorry.
It's okay.
One, two, three, four.
I need to get more out.
Smells good.
Could you taste this?
Sure.
Be careful, it's hot.
Wait.
Oh, someone must be here already.
You're earlier than I expected.
Yes.
Hello.
Well...
This is...
Uh, hey...
Could you taste this soup for me?
Sure.
How is it?
I think
it's a little bland.
Really?
I think it's fine.
Oh, really?
Is it?
Is it bland?
I'm not sure.
- What's wrong?
No,
the seasoning seems fine.
Why are you two acting so natural?
- Should I let it boil a bit more then?
- No.
It might get too salty. I think it's fine now.
Are you doing okay?
The fire just won't start.
Oh? I haven't seen this before.
Did we always have this?
I bought a new one.
I wondered if I'd actually use it much.
But I thought having it would make me use it.
That was a good idea.
I'm home.
- Hi.
- You're home.
Hi, Bom.
You remember me, right?
Have you been doing well?
Hello.
Ah, yeah.
He's handsome, unlike you.
What?
I'm not bad-looking myself.
Look. Smoke follows handsome people.
I'll get it.
Yeah.
Jun Seo.
- Long time no see.
- Yeah.
It has been a while.
- Please come in.
- Yes.
Come on in. You have to say hello.
Welcome.
Hello.
You must be Daniel.
You're handsome, just like your dad.
- Here... this is for you.
- Oh, you shouldn't have.
Come this way, please.
Hello.
This is for me?
It's so pretty.
Okay, please take a seat.
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy it.
He still doesn't know how to make a ssam.
You need to add garlic and peppers
when you eat meat.
- Here.
- Oh, come on.
- Dad.
- Just add one more.
Oh, Dad.
It's spicy so it cuts the grease.
It's good. Try it.
How is it? Good, right?
Oh, don't eat it. Gosh.
What's wrong?
- It's too spicy.
- Oh my goodness.
- Water, please.
- Dad!
[Tonight, he weighs heavily on her heart]
Hey.
Oh, seriously.
Dad, he can't handle spicy food.
No, definitely not.
Are you okay?
Just swallow it. Swallow it.
Do you want to spit it out?
Look how red his face is.
- I'm going out for a bit.
- Okay.
Let's toast with water.
Cheers.
[Matna Pork Cutlet]
Only pork cutlet? Isn't it dry?
One jjolmyeon, please.
What are you doing?
It was a little painful,
not seeing you for a few days
and not being able
to contact you.
I didn't realize it before,
but actually, I...
I think I like cutting pork cutlets for you.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
I like stealing the cutlet I cut for you.
And I love
the loud way you eat the pork cutlet
that I sliced for you.
So...
So what?
So, this is on me.
Gosh.
Just this?
Hey.
I'm still a student.
Eat this.
Say, "Ah."
Is it good?
Yeah.
Is it that good?
The summer that was unusually loud
and hot
was coming to an end like this.
And just like that, the seasons passed.
And other seasons
arrived.
[Driving test vehicle]
Some seasons taught me
that things I feared
weren't actually that big of a deal.
Vehicle No. 15, you passed.
Seasons that gave us the joy
of growing to resemble each other
in our clumsiness.
Seasons that marked the end
of long-held plans and preparations.
[Congrats on resigning, future great writer!]
Ta-da!
Congrats on resigning!
No matter how much we anticipated and prepared,
there were seasons
where sadness was unavoidable.
Thank you for coming to me as my daughter.
Thank you
for making me a mom.
Through all the bitter,
healing,
warm,
fluttering,
and cold moments...
several seasons
have stacked up behind us,
and now,
a new spring
is blooming.
[Welcome, new students of Seongeun University!]
Five minutes left.
Holding onto it now means there's no hope.
Just a few more seconds, please!
Sure.
Even those five minutes
are part of your hard-earned tuition.
Use it all.
Hello, TA.
Long time no see.
Yeah, it really has been a while.
- Hello, Professor.
- Hello.
I'm so jealous.
Look at you, Professor.
Stick close to Professor Song too.
You never know.
Come on... me?
Since you're done, let's grab a meal.
I have a class,
so I have to head to Ansan. Sorry.
Oh, okay.
Bye.
I'm being so pathetic, aren't I?
Just awful.
Well...
You're acting sentimental,
unlike your usual self.
It's actually kind of sexy.
You dated for so long,
and finally, it's happening.
Of course. Too much time invested
in breaking up.
Everyone uses mobile invites these days.
They insisted on doing every little thing
for the wedding.
I heard they almost broke up over it.
I'm not giving you the bouquet.
I'm heading out first.
You didn't forget next Saturday, right?
Right, I won't forget.
- I'm heading off now.
- Have a good one.
Bye.
I think I'm gonna be late.
Traffic is bad.
What about the flowers? Did you get them?
Shoot! What should I do?
It'll take too long to find a florist.
Then...
I'll buy them! Just get there quickly.
Drive safely,
but hurry up!
[Daniel, you're the best!]
Everyone else is already out here...
Isn't it that way?
- Dad.
- Yeah.
Congrats! You were amazing.
I thought you were going to smash the drums.
Total
Aerosmith vibes.
No.
I wasn't that good.
He's sweating quite a lot.
Daniel.
Mom!
When did you get here?
I got here yesterday.
Long time no see.
Yeah.
Hello.
Oh... Hello.
I've heard a lot about you.